{
	"records":[
		{
			"question":"2 x 4 =",
			"answer":8
		},
		{
			"question":"6 x 2 =",
			"answer":12
		},
		{
			"question":"5 x 5 =",
			"answer":25
		},
		{
			"question":"2 x 8 =",
			"answer":16
		},
		{
			"question":"8 x 5 =",
			"answer":40
		},
		{
			"question":"7 x 4 =",
			"answer":28
		},
		{
			"question":"9 x 3 =",
			"answer":27
		},
		{
			"question":"7 x 3 =",
			"answer":21
		},
		{
			"question":"8 x 4 =",
			"answer":32
		},
		{
			"question":"10 x 2 =",
			"answer":20
		},
		{
			"question":"1 x 9 =",
			"answer":9
		},
		{
			"question":"4 x 6 =",
			"answer":24
		},
		{
			"question":"9 x 4 =",
			"answer":36
		},
		{
			"question":"5 x 6 =",
			"answer":30
		},
		{
			"question":"9 x 5 =",
			"answer":45
		},
		{
			"question":"5 x 7 =",
			"answer":35
		},
		{
			"question":"8 x 3 =",
			"answer":24
		},
		{
			"question":"9 x 2 =",
			"answer":18
		},
		{
			"question":"10 x 5 =",
			"answer":50
		},
		{
			"question":"4 x 7 =",
			"answer":28
		},
		{
			"question":"3 x 8 =",
			"answer":24
		},
		{
			"question":"2 x 5 =",
			"answer":10
		},
		{
			"question":"3 x 1 =",
			"answer":3
		},
		{
			"question":"9 x 0 =",
			"answer":0
		},
		{
			"question":"7 x 1 =",
			"answer":7
		},
		{
			"question":"4 x 6 =",
			"answer":24
		},
		{
			"question":"2 x 6 =",
			"answer":12
		},
		{
			"question":"10 x 10 =",
			"answer":100
		},
		{
			"question":"4 x 4 =",
			"answer":16
		},
		{
			"question":"2 x 7 =",
			"answer":14
		},
		{
			"question":"8 x 1 =",
			"answer":8
		},
		{
			"question":"8 x 0 =",
			"answer":0
		},
		{
			"question":"9 x 2 =",
			"answer":18
		},
		{
			"question":"6 x 0 =",
			"answer":0
		},
		{
			"question":"2 x 1 =",
			"answer":2
		},
		{
			"question":"5 x 4 =",
			"answer":20
		},
		{
			"question":"8 x 10 =",
			"answer":80
		},
		{
			"question":"10 x 9 =",
			"answer":90
		},
		{
			"question":"5 x 5 =",
			"answer":25
		},
		{
			"question":"7 x 1 =",
			"answer":7
		},
		{
			"question":"4 x 3 =",
			"answer":12
		},
		{
			"question":"3 x 7 =",
			"answer":21
		},
		{
			"question":"8 x 4 =",
			"answer":32
		},
		{
			"question":"9 x 4 =",
			"answer":36
		},
		{
			"question":"6 x 5 =",
			"answer":30
		},
		{
			"question":"7 x 10 =",
			"answer":70
		},
		{
			"question":"8 x 2 =",
			"answer":16
		},
		{
			"question":"8 x 5 =",
			"answer":40
		},
		{
			"question":"7 x 4 =",
			"answer":28
		},
		{
			"question":"4 x 9 =",
			"answer":36
		},
		{
			"question":"8 x 4 =",
			"answer":32
		},
		{
			"question":"7 x 0 =",
			"answer":0
		},
		{
			"question":"5 x 4 =",
			"answer":20
		},
		{
			"question":"10 x 6 =",
			"answer":60
		},
		{
			"question":"8 x 1 =",
			"answer":8
		},
		{
			"question":"5 x 9 =",
			"answer":45
		},
		{
			"question":"8 x 5 =",
			"answer":40
		},
		{
			"question":"6 x 1 =",
			"answer":6
		},
		{
			"question":"4 x 0 =",
			"answer":0
		},
		{
			"question":"7 x 10 =",
			"answer":70
		},
		{
			"question":"6 x 4 =",
			"answer":24
		},
		{
			"question":"5 x 8 =",
			"answer":40
		},
		{
			"question":"9 x 5 =",
			"answer":45
		},
		{
			"question":"6 x 0 =",
			"answer":0
		},
		{
			"question":"1 x 9 =",
			"answer":9
		},
		{
			"question":"8 x 2 =",
			"answer":16
		},
		{
			"question":"7 x 5 =",
			"answer":35
		},
		{
			"question":"6 x 4 =",
			"answer":24
		},
		{
			"question":"9 x 3 =",
			"answer":27
		},
		{
			"question":"2 x 9 =",
			"answer":18
		},
		{
			"question":"6 x 3 =",
			"answer":18
		},
		{
			"question":"7 x 4 =",
			"answer":28
		},
		{
			"question":"9 x 2 =",
			"answer":18
		},
		{
			"question":"3 x 7 =",
			"answer":21
		},
		{
			"question":"7 x 3 =",
			"answer":21
		},
		{
			"question":"0 x 5 =",
			"answer":0
		},
		{
			"question":"10 x 4 =",
			"answer":40
		},
		{
			"question":"8 x 10 =",
			"answer":80
		},
		{
			"question":"1 x 2 =",
			"answer":2
		},
		{
			"question":"3 x 2 =",
			"answer":6
		},
		{
			"question":"3 x 3 =",
			"answer":9
		},
		{
			"question":"10 x 6 =",
			"answer":60
		},
		{
			"question":"4 x 9 =",
			"answer":36
		},
		{
			"question":"2 x 2 =",
			"answer":4
		},
		{
			"question":"1 x 6 =",
			"answer":6
		},
		{
			"question":"4 x 1 =",
			"answer":4
		},
		{
			"question":"0 x 7 =",
			"answer":0
		},
		{
			"question":"3 x 8 =",
			"answer":24
		},
		{
			"question":"9 x 5 =",
			"answer":45
		},
		{
			"question":"6 x 2 =",
			"answer":12
		},
		{
			"question":"7 x 2 =",
			"answer":14
		},
		{
			"question":"2 x 5 =",
			"answer":10
		},
		{
			"question":"5 x 6 =",
			"answer":30
		},
		{
			"question":"10 x 8 =",
			"answer":80
		},
		{
			"question":"10 x 0 =",
			"answer":0
		},
		{
			"question":"5x8=",
			"answer":40
		},
		{
			"question":"2 x 9 =",
			"answer":18
		},
		{
			"question":"10 x 10 =",
			"answer":100
		},
		{
			"question":"3 x 5 =",
			"answer":15
		},
		{
			"question":"5 x 5 =",
			"answer":25
		}
	]
}